motorbiscuit.com 2019-11-29

# Privacy Policy | MotorBiscuit.com

EndGame360 Inc. respects the privacy of our Readers. Ensuring that you understand what personal information is gathered and how it is used is of paramount importance to us.

This Privacy Policy outlines what personal information EndGame360 Inc. gathers, who within the company has access to that information, how we store it, and also explains the handling of any personal information shared with third parties who process your data on our behalf while serving ads to you, or as we gather site analytics to improve your experience with us.

What information do we collect?

We collect personal information from you when you visit our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When registering for our newsletters you will be asked to enter your name and email address. Your subscription preferences will be saved in order to ensure proper delivery of the newsletter(s) you wish to receive.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include clear unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

In order to customize your experience on EndGame360 Inc. and tailor the advertisements to your personal interests, we automatically receive data from your browser when you visit our site. This information indirectly identifies you and is not associated with your personal identity as it relates to data storage. The data automatically received through our ad serving system is as follows: your device, web browser, IP address, operating system, and potentially also your geolocation and time zone.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is stored in a database, only to be accessible by those EndGame360 Inc. employees and third-party services authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information secure and confidential.

Do we share your data?

Yes. We share your personal data with third parties who process your data on our behalf when they provide services to us, for example, data analytics, ad serving networks, and our email marketing service.

We may potentially be required by law to disclose or share your personal data without your consent in some circumstances, for example, to comply with a court order or law enforcement.

Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

Our cookies do not contain personal information or link to you as an individual.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Third party cookies

Third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information on this website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. There are several options available to you would prefer to opt-out of the collection and use of information for ad targeting.

Please visit the following links for more information and to opt-out: www.aboutads.info/choices

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

EAA opt-out: [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our Terms of Service.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This Privacy Policy was last modified on February 6, 2019.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices you may contact us using the following information:

PO Box 8912  
Asheville, NC 28814  
United States
